{
        "name": "space_odyssey",
        "rooms": [
          {
            "name": "the dark hallway",
            "song": "madworld.wav",
            "description": "Lights flickering down a dark hallway",
            "requiredItem": {"name": "none", "inscription":""},
            "actor": {
            "name": "Diego the Wide Mouthed Duck",
            "actorRoomText": "In the distance you see what looks like a duck, oh wait, it is Diego the wide mouthed Duck with a bill full of... Guts?",
            "secretText": "Quack quack quack, before you put me down, let Bunny bunny big skins know that I love him",
            "dialogs": [
              "I have some cards, but im not sure what to do, answer my question while I think it through.",
              "Come fight me baby... [Diego blows you a kiss.]",
              "Quack Quack, Diego seems to have vanished, you hear quacking in the distance"
            ],
            "item":
              {
                "name": "Willie Mays 1952 Topps #261 Giants Baseball Card",
                "inscription": "Base ball gloves fits all...IV"
              },
            "trivia": [
              {
                "question": "How long would the Sun have to be out before people realzied it?",
                "answers": ["1min", "4min", "8min", "12min"],
                "correctAnswer": "8min"
              },
              {
                "question": "Many birds have a gland that produces a waxy oil to waterproof feathers called a _____ gland?",
                "answers": ["Mandrake", "Drake", "Uropygial", "Duckle"],
                "correctAnswer": "Uropygial"
              },
              {
                "question": "How long after hatching are Ducklings able to walk and leave the nest?",
                "answers": ["immediately", "a couple hours", "a day", "a couple days"],
                "correctAnswer": "a couple hours"
              },
              {
                "question": "a group of ducks can be called a ______?",
                "answers": ["druid", "deckle", "cast", "raft"],
                "correctAnswer": "raft"
              },
              {
                "question": "How many eyelids does a duck have?",
                "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
                "correctAnswer": "3"
              }
            ]
          }
          ,
          "adjacent_rooms": ["storage closet", "the dark room", "the disco hole", "the broken mirror", "mysterious door"]
        },
          {
            "name": "storage closet",
            "song": "madworld.wav",
            "description": "You've entered a storage closet, what looked like a 3 by 4 square seems to have stretched into a large open area of nothingness",
            "requiredItem":{"name": "Willie Mays 1952 Topps #261 Giants Baseball Card", "inscription":""},
            "actor": {
              "name": "Bunny Bunny Big Skins",
              "actorRoomText": "You see 'Bunny Bunny Big Skins' sitting in the corner of the room chopping away at a carrot",
              "secretText": "Oh god, what are you doing? Whats wrong with you, please don't hurt me!!! AHHHHH!!!",
              "dialogs": [
                "So you think you can escape, answer a question if you want my help.",
                "Oh, so this is how it is? hope you weren't planning on getting out of here.",
                "Thump Thump [The sound of Bunny feet slapping the ground], so long, good luck, Thump thump thump thump thump"
              ],
              "item":
              {
                "name": "brass knuckle",
                "inscription": "the sun can be represented by the number... VII"
              },
              "trivia": [
                {
                  "question": "What is added to steel to makes it 'Stainless', 'Tastless', and prevents 'Oxidation'? ",
                  "answers": ["Chromium", "Silicon", "Manganses", "Carbon"],
                  "correctAnswer": "Chromium"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Many birds have a gland that produces a waxy oil to waterproof feathers called a _____ gland?",
                  "answers": ["Mandrake", "Drake", "Uropygial", "Duckle"],
                  "correctAnswer": "Uropygial"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How long after hatching are Ducklings able to walk and leave the nest?",
                  "answers": ["immediately", "a couple hours", "a day", "a couple days"],
                  "correctAnswer": "a couple hours"
                },
                {
                  "question": "a group of ducks can be called a ______?",
                  "answers": ["druid", "deckle", "cast", "raft"],
                  "correctAnswer": "raft"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How many eyelids does a duck have?",
                  "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
                  "correctAnswer": "3"
                }
              ]
            },
            "adjacent_rooms": ["the dark hallway"]
          },
          {
            "name": "the dark room",
            "song": "madworld.wav",
            "description": "You've entered the Dark room, if you peer into the darkness long enough, eventually it looks back into you...",
            "requiredItem":{"name": "Willie Mays 1952 Topps #261 Giants Baseball Card", "inscription":""},
            "actor": {
              "name": "Mad Bat",
              "actorRoomText": "Deep in the darkness of you can only see the light of the room ahead, from the ceiling you hear a crunching, CRUNCH CRUNCH CRUNCH, the sounds of beetle bones snapping in Mad Bats mouth",
              "secretText": "..... [Mad Bat Parishes in Silence]",
              "dialogs": [
                "CRUNCH CRUNCH CRUNCH, You dare interrupt my feast, answer me now before I hang you by your feet...",
                "How do you expect to fight me in the darkness when you cant see me, but i can see you?",
                "Swoosh Swoosh... Mad Bat flys away"
              ],
              "item":
              {
                "name": "Baccarat Zodiac Pig",
                "inscription": "socks and shoes both come in... III"
              },
              "trivia": [
                {
                  "question": "Which animal has pink milk?",
                  "answers": ["Eastern Salmon", "Rhinos", "Platypus", "Hippopotamus"],
                  "correctAnswer": "Hippopotamus"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Many birds have a gland that produces a waxy oil to waterproof feathers called a _____ gland?",
                  "answers": ["Mandrake", "Drake", "Uropygial", "Duckle"],
                  "correctAnswer": "Uropygial"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How long after hatching are Ducklings able to walk and leave the nest?",
                  "answers": ["immediately", "a couple hours", "a day", "a couple days"],
                  "correctAnswer": "a couple hours"
                },
                {
                  "question": "a group of ducks can be called a ______?",
                  "answers": ["druid", "deckle", "cast", "raft"],
                  "correctAnswer": "raft"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How many eyelids does a duck have?",
                  "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
                  "correctAnswer": "3"
                }
              ]
            },
            "adjacent_rooms": ["the dark hallway", "the bathroom"]
          },
          {
            "name": "the bathroom",
            "song": "hurt.wav",
            "description": " You've entered the bathroom, it obviously hasn't been cleaned in days",
            "requiredItem":{"name": "Baccarat Zodiac Pig", "inscription":""},
            "actor": {
              "name": "Arty the Alligator",
              "actorRoomText": "the smell of fish and cheap cologne permeate your nostrils , you look down and see Arty the Alligator with his mouth wide open",
              "secretText": "Oh shit, how did this happen... Let me go my friend, it was just a game... Please don't, I have kids, we'll there my sisters kids, but i love them like my own... ok, you got me i don't have a sister... Oh noo....",
              "dialogs": [
                "You can quit now, just step inside, or answer my question, either way you will die.",
                "So you want to be my meal of the day?",
                "Chomp Chomp Chomp Chomp, Arty barrels through the floor"
              ],
              "item":
              {
                "name": "Snake skin assless chaps",
                "inscription": "...Rainbows have so many colors... II"
              },
              "trivia": [
                {
                  "question": " An adult male duck is referred to as a _____?",
                  "answers": ["Mandrake", "Drake", "Quacker", "Duckle"],
                  "correctAnswer": "Drake"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Many birds have a gland that produces a waxy oil to waterproof feathers called a _____ gland?",
                  "answers": ["Mandrake", "Drake", "Uropygial", "Duckle"],
                  "correctAnswer": "Uropygial"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How long after hatching are Ducklings able to walk and leave the nest?",
                  "answers": ["immediately", "a couple hours", "a day", "a couple days"],
                  "correctAnswer": "a couple hours"
                },
                {
                  "question": "a group of ducks can be called a ______?",
                  "answers": ["druid", "deckle", "cast", "raft"],
                  "correctAnswer": "raft"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How many eyelids does a duck have?",
                  "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
                  "correctAnswer": "3"
                }
              ]
            },
            "adjacent_rooms": ["the dark room", "the disco hole"]
          },
          {
            "name": "the disco hole",
            "song": "hurt.wav",
            "description": "You have entered the disco hole, energy levels are high, your foot starts to slap uncontrollably against the floor as horrible 80's music floods your ears.",
            "requiredItem":{"name": "Snake skin assless chaps", "inscription":""},
            "actor": {
              "name": "Filthy the Bear",
              "actorRoomText": "Filthy the Bear is staring into a cheap vanity putting on lipstick, smoke is rising from an ashtray, you can taste ",
              "secretText": "Come on baby, it was just a joke, here take what you want, i'm too pretty to die like this...",
              "dialogs": [
                "Owww youre kind of cute, you should just stay here with me for the night",
                "Oh, you're no fun, well not yet... you'll be plenty fun when you're dead!",
                "Filthy Implodes causing what looks like a rift in time?"
              ],
              "item":
              {
                "name": "Dirty Handkerchief",
                "inscription": "to my love, Filthy, in memory of the magic ball we had... V"
              },
              "trivia": [
                {
                  "question": "If you have 23 pairs of people what is the chance that two of them share the same birthday?",
                  "answers": ["50%", "25%", "23%", "7%"],
                  "correctAnswer": "50%"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Many birds have a gland that produces a waxy oil to waterproof feathers called a _____ gland?",
                  "answers": ["Mandrake", "Drake", "Uropygial", "Duckle"],
                  "correctAnswer": "Uropygial"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How long after hatching are Ducklings able to walk and leave the nest?",
                  "answers": ["immediately", "a couple hours", "a day", "a couple days"],
                  "correctAnswer": "a couple hours"
                },
                {
                  "question": "a group of ducks can be called a ______?",
                  "answers": ["druid", "deckle", "cast", "raft"],
                  "correctAnswer": "raft"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How many eyelids does a duck have?",
                  "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
                  "correctAnswer": "3"
                }
              ]
            },
            "adjacent_rooms": ["the bathroom"]
          },
          {
            "name": "the broken mirror",
            "song": "hurt.wav",
            "description": "You have fallen through a broken mirror",
            "requiredItem": {"name": "Dirty handkerchief", "inscription":""},
            "actor": {
              "name": "Frisky Whiskers",
              "actorRoomText": "You've entered an empty white room, you hear upbeat 80s music, Madonna maybe?, towards the center you see a massive Lion wearing a hot pink blazer working out to a Richard Simmons workout video...",
              "secretText": "We could of danced the night away but you had to ruin it didn't you.",
              "dialogs": [
                "I've always practiced this; Love yourself, move your body. Watch your portions...",
                "Number one, like yourself. Number two, you have to eat healthy. And number three, you've got to squeeze your buns. That's my formula... Lets DANCE",
                "You're getting warm... If you're not hangin around, I guess i'll catch you later Traveler"
              ],
              "item":
              {
                "name": "Pioneer 8 Track Stereo Model H-R99",
                "inscription": "cool cats never die, the have many lives. VI"
              },
              "trivia": [
                {
                  "question": "If you have a pie how many cuts would it take to make 8 slices?",
                  "answers": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
                  "correctAnswer": "3"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Many birds have a gland that produces a waxy oil to waterproof feathers called a _____ gland?",
                  "answers": ["Mandrake", "Drake", "Uropygial", "Duckle"],
                  "correctAnswer": "Uropygial"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How long after hatching are Ducklings able to walk and leave the nest?",
                  "answers": ["immediately", "a couple hours", "a day", "a couple days"],
                  "correctAnswer": "a couple hours"
                },
                {
                  "question": "a group of ducks can be called a ______?",
                  "answers": ["druid", "deckle", "cast", "raft"],
                  "correctAnswer": "raft"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How many eyelids does a duck have?",
                  "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
                  "correctAnswer": "3"
                }
              ]
            },
            "adjacent_rooms": ["big daddys lair", "the dark hallway"]
          },
          {
            "name": "big daddys lair",
            "song": "hurt.wav",
            "description": "You've stepped into big daddies lair, are you ready for some big daddy? ",
            "requiredItem":{"name": "Pioneer 8 Track Stereo Model H-R99", "inscription":""},
            "actor": {
              "name": "Big Daddy the Devilishly Handsome Donkey",
              "actorRoomText": "Flames light up against the wall, toward the back of the room sits a Donkey on a suede Throne his snout buried in a bucket full of mice, you can hear their little squeeks as their bones pop between the donkeys bloody teeth",
              "secretText": "Oh, no, how could this be, Big Daddy was taken down by someone like you... ",
              "dialogs": [
                "Hey hey hey, [Big Daddy stares at your jacket], That's a nice jacket you have there, can I try it on? ",
                "They call me Big Daddy for a reason, I guess its time to tumble.... HeeHaw",
                "HeeHaw Looks like you're done here... \nYou follow Big Daddy through a dark corridor into an empty ballroom with a keypad sitting in the middle of the floor."
              ],
              "item":
              {
                "name": "Pioneer 8 Track Stereo Model H-R99",
                "inscription": "cool cats never die, the have many lives. VIII"
              },
              "trivia": [
                {
                  "question": "How many seconds are there in a year?",
                  "answers": ["31,556,926", "9,333,334", "67,877,323,432", "234,876"],
                  "correctAnswer": "31,556,926"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Many birds have a gland that produces a waxy oil to waterproof feathers called a _____ gland?",
                  "answers": ["Mandrake", "Drake", "Uropygial", "Duckle"],
                  "correctAnswer": "Uropygial"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How long after hatching are Ducklings able to walk and leave the nest?",
                  "answers": ["immediately", "a couple hours", "a day", "a couple days"],
                  "correctAnswer": "a couple hours"
                },
                {
                  "question": "a group of ducks can be called a ______?",
                  "answers": ["druid", "deckle", "cast", "raft"],
                  "correctAnswer": "raft"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How many eyelids does a duck have?",
                  "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
                  "correctAnswer": "3"
                }
              ]
            },
            "adjacent_rooms": ["the broken mirror"]
          },
          {
            "name": "mysterious door",
            "song": "sound.wav",
            "description": "You've passed through the Mysterious Door and now find yourself in a kaleidoscope dream\nGravity seems to have increased, it's hard to stand",
            "requiredItem":{"name": "Pioneer 8 Track Stereo Model H-R99", "inscription":""},
            "actor": {
              "name": "Lyssa, Daughter of Nyx",
              "actorRoomText": "Towards the center of the room sits a pale faced women, adorned in a tattered dress, playing a lune",
              "secretText": "Thank you for saving me from my madness, this place has grown heavy on my soul",
              "dialogs": [
                "Please, keep away, I don't want to hurt you",
                "Lyssa goes into a mad rage and the room is seemingly warping",
                "... farewell... Lyssa seemingly melts into the floor"
              ],
              "item":
              {
                "name": "Lyssas flute",
                "inscription": "It seems life could not grant us with the love we deserved, now we look to the gods in the sky... I"
              },
              "trivia": [
                {
                  "question": "How many planets are named after Gods from mythology?",
                  "answers": ["3", "4", "7", "8"],
                  "correctAnswer": "7"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Many birds have a gland that produces a waxy oil to waterproof feathers called a _____ gland?",
                  "answers": ["Mandrake", "Drake", "Uropygial", "Duckle"],
                  "correctAnswer": "Uropygial"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How long after hatching are Ducklings able to walk and leave the nest?",
                  "answers": ["immediately", "a couple hours", "a day", "a couple days"],
                  "correctAnswer": "a couple hours"
                },
                {
                  "question": "a group of ducks can be called a ______?",
                  "answers": ["druid", "deckle", "cast", "raft"],
                  "correctAnswer": "raft"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How many eyelids does a duck have?",
                  "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
                  "correctAnswer": "3"
                }
              ]
            },
            "adjacent_rooms": ["the dark hallway", "long stairwell"]
          },
          {
            "name": "long stairwell",
            "song": "sound.wav",
            "description": "You entered a stairwell which seemed to have no end...\nFinally it comes to an end, you can no longer see the light from the doorway from which you came but only an old steel door that seems to have been barred shut.\nYou should probably turn back",
            "requiredItem": {"name": "Lyssas Flute", "inscription":""},
            "actor": {
              "name": "Mak",
              "actorRoomText": "You turn around to leave and but you feel a pull at your arm",
              "secretText": "As the paths ahead are certain to be dark, I shall certainly be with you...",
              "dialogs": [
                "I've always practiced this; Love yourself, move your body. Watch your portions...",
                "Midway upon the journey of life we have found ourselves in this forest dark, your path ends here...",
                "Mak releases you arm, you should probably leave..."
              ],
              "item":
              {
                "name": "7th ring of Hell",
                "inscription": "unlucky friday... IX-X"
              },
              "trivia": [
                {
                  "question": " An adult male duck is referred to as a _____?",
                  "answers": ["Mandrake", "Drake", "Quacker", "Duckle"],
                  "correctAnswer": "Drake"
                },
                {
                  "question": "Many birds have a gland that produces a waxy oil to waterproof feathers called a _____ gland?",
                  "answers": ["Mandrake", "Drake", "Uropygial", "Duckle"],
                  "correctAnswer": "Uropygial"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How long after hatching are Ducklings able to walk and leave the nest?",
                  "answers": ["immediately", "a couple hours", "a day", "a couple days"],
                  "correctAnswer": "a couple hours"
                },
                {
                  "question": "a group of ducks can be called a ______?",
                  "answers": ["druid", "deckle", "cast", "raft"],
                  "correctAnswer": "raft"
                },
                {
                  "question": "How many eyelids does a duck have?",
                  "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
                  "correctAnswer": "3"
                }
              ]
            },
            "adjacent_rooms": ["mysterious door"]
          }
        ]
}